calm
покой
shop sound
магазин звук поговорим
let's talk Here you listen to the song Katyusha took care of
Вот вы дослушайте песню
but it was a little redone why
но она немножко переделанная зачем
the Soviet song was redone to distort Soviet
было советская песня коверкать советские
songs military this blasphemy no
песни военные это кощунство нет
fought Here you listen then
воевал Вот вы послушайте потом
look again here my grandfather fought
смотрите еще раз вот у меня дед воевал и
and you can
у вас
imagine if we will be
представляете если мы будем
Soviet songs about the war
Советский песни про войну
my grandfather is yours, this is really Katyusha’s song, how
дед мой ваш вот реально песню Катюша как
she was changing
она была менять
this feeling, it’s like
это чувство это все равно что
taking and
взять и
tormenting yourself on your grandfather’s grave
помучиться на могилу деда
if you have where your waves are
если у вас где твои волны вы Один хер
flag of
обязательно сидеть под флагом
you somewhere by the way where you fought. This is your
Вас где-то кстати где воевал Это Ваше
desire. Your grandfather, where he ended up near Moscow,
желание ваш Дед где он попал под Москвой
disappeared
пропал
like
как это
this, but even my great-grandfather fought for me,
вот так но это даже прадед у меня воевал
having done 4 it should have been what four
проделав 4 должно было быть какие четыре
four what you tell me where
четыре что вы рассказываете откуда
I should know them
я их должна знать
tell you the math from where  4
рассказываю вам математику откуда 4
pridedens You have one dad, so
прайдена У вас есть один папа так
if you take
если у родителей брать
grandfathers from your parents, you have two great-grandfathers that not
дедов у вас два прадедов о том что не
everyone remembers  grandfathers and great-grandfathers, you didn’t think
все помнят дедов и прадедов вы не думали
about it at all, your
об этом вообще у вас
grandmother only told me about one
мне бабушка только про одного
There were four of them,
рассказывала Всего их четыре было просто
you just might not know some, maybe
вы некоторых может не знать может быть
she was small Maybe she had
она была маленькой Может она
two grandfathers, one of your grandfather disappeared or about
дедов два один дед у вас пропал или про
one Your mom has your dad  mom dad and
У вашего мамы папа у вашей мамы папа и
your dad do you know which one of them you know
вашей папы Вы кого из них знаете
Two grandfathers you have but you already say great-grandfathers
Два деда У вас есть но вы прадедов уже
I will pass you two grandfathers somewhere
говорить Я пройду вас Два деда где-то 2
2 there
уже нет
were two
было два
there were two grandfathers
было Два деда
Yes, and the second Wait, and the
неизвестно Да а второй Подождите а
second When you last saw him,
второй Когда вы его последний раз видели
I heard it, I didn’t see it from stories How
слышали я не видела это по рассказам Как
could I hear about my great-grandfathers that
я могла про своих прадедов слышать что
until my great-grandfather and the second grandfather he
пока не прадеду а второй дед он где-то
fought somewhere or not
воевал или нет
I don’t know about this damn thing, the deduction just
Я не знаю про это блин просто вычета мне
tells me  Everyone who throws me about grandfathers
говорит Все кто мне закидывает про дедов
and the flag Yes, I start to say something
и флаг Да я что-то начинаю придет
and everyone doesn’t immediately know grandfathers,
говорить и все что-то дедов сразу не
and then I know my
знают и тогда вот я своего деда знаю дед
grandfather, my grandfather died after the war, but he didn’t
у меня уже после войны погиб но он не
fight I know about my great-grandfather for sure  what I
воевал Я знаю про прадеда точно что у
have here, look, they started
меня вот смотрите начали
such a site the memory of the people there you can drive in the
такой сайт память народа там можно вбить
last name, first name, patronymic of your grandfather, great-grandfather
фамилия имя отчество своего деда прадеда
and see where I fought for what
и посмотреть где воевал за что награжден
I was awarded mine.
я своего У меня нет
I'm
вы сами начали жить вы не начали мне
kidding you have some kind of flag hanging there for your
шучу у тебя там какая-то флаг висит за
grandfathers But you should be ashamed of your grandfathers
дедов Но вам стыдно должно у вас деды
fought for the Germans, so they are not in the
воевали за немцев значит их в базе
Soviet base yes this is your house I can
Советской нету да это ваш дом я могу
take my great-grandfather's case here he fought
своего прадеда взять дело вот он воевал
where he fought what for what he was awarded you can
где воевал что за что награжден можете
at least  one in front of you That is, your
хотя бы одного перед вами То есть у вас
grandfather didn’t fight for the Soviet Union Yes, they found a
Дед за Советский Союз не воевал Да нашли
fascist, I’ll tell you why Because because
вот я скажу почему Потому что потому что
you fought your grandfather fought for Hitler And
вы воевали ваши дед воевал за Гитлера А
now you’re distorting well and turning
вы сейчас исковерка ну и Катюшу
on Katyusha
включаете
If you had a memory of children, you
Если бы у вас было память о дети вы бы
would  they didn’t do the
так не делали
so-called
так называемые
ears,
ушками
he’s not in the Soviet database, but you want to
его нету в базе Советской а вы хотите
look at my grandfather seriously, seriously,
моего деда посмотреть серьезно серьезно
I say you want to tell me Yes, what kind of Grandfather I
говорю хотите скажите Да какой Дед я
can only show a
могу только фотографию показать
photo of a photo of any ka  for now,
фотографию любого какой-то деда пока что
tell me your grandfather’s last name, patronymic of your grandfather
скажите фамилия имя отчество деда вашего
But actually Who am I so that I
А вот собственно Кто такой чтобы я перед
’m not going to you, you’re already
Я не собираюсь перед вами вы уже
crucifying goodbye Katyusha ran away
распинаетесь до свидания убежала Катюша
so impudent it was because your
такая дерзкая было потому что ваша
look in Russia about a million people
смотрите в России около миллиона человек
fought for Hitler where these are all
воевала за Гитлера где эти все
The heirs of these now sitting in front of me are the
Наследники этих вот сидит передо мной
heiress of my grandfather who fought for
сейчас наследница деда который воевал за
Hitler Because those grandfathers who
Гитлера Потому что те деды которые
fought for the Soviet Union can be found
воевали за Советский Союз их можно найти
in the database to look at and here I don’t know my
в базе посмотреть а тут деда не знаю
grandfather, my great-grandfather didn’t become at all I don’t know anyone
прадеда не стал вообще никого не знаю
so Let’s check Or
так Давайте проверим Или действительно
maybe he really fought for  fought Hitler,
он воевал может он за гитлерова воевал
then Ukraine didn’t exist then the
Украины тогда не было тогда был
Soviet Union was
Советский Союз
in 41, it didn’t exist such a country
в 41 году его не было такой страны
I don’t know your history I didn’t teach it
Я не знаю вашу историю не учил
don’t open your filthy mouth about
не открывайте свой такой поганый рот про
our history, learn history Because it’s
нашу историю выучите историю Потому что
impossible not to say it’s known it’s impossible
нельзя чтобы не говорила известно нельзя
to
чтобы
fight for the Nazis  the army was tied up the
воевали за гитлеров это армия власована
Russian liberation army, all these
русская освободительная армия все эти
Cossack regiments Yes, they fought for Hitler, they
казачьи полки Да воевали за Гитлера
killed our grandfathers  and now he sits and
убивали наших дедов и теперь сидит и
turns on some work of
включает нам какой-то работку Катюши
Katyusha to explain to you it’s on your conscience
вам объяснять выходит на ваши совести
you rotten pagan granddaughter Slava Ukraine
вас гнилой языцкая внучка Слава Украина
sits Piglet is like that tell us about
сидит Хрюня такая рассказывай нам про
everyone’s grandfathers
дедов у всех короче да
so let’s go further pancake Everything is shorter at once
так едем дальше блин Все короче сразу
grandfathers are your tomatoes Like this they
деды ваши помидоры Типа такая они
separate them like  fought yes And our
отмежевывают их типа воевали да А наши
grandfathers In short, something is wrong, but when
деды Короче что-то не так но когда
you start to sort it out for everyone,
начинаешь разбирать у каждого
it turns out that they have something wrong with the dynamos,
оказывается что у них с динами не так
I don’t remember a part at all Okay, I don’t remember my
тут не часть вообще не помню
great-grandfather But damn their grandfather
Ладно прадеда не помнить Но блин деда их
So the surname was what's the problem
звали Так фамилия была в чем проблема